♪～
A voice heard in the distance gives me a hint.
tooku de kikoeru koe wo hinto ni
One by one like-minded people are standing up.
hitori mata hitori tachiagaru doushi
Lets overturn all the everyday, monotonous things.
kurikaesu dake no fudan doori kutsugaesu
I'm ready, are you ready?
junbi iize are you ready
A shiver spreads through my body, violently ringing stomping.
karadajuu furuwasu shindou ni hageshiku uchinarase yo stomping
Constantly stirring in me, it calls me.
taezu tsuki ugokasu call me
Catching that unchanging, never wavering story, Come on!
kawarazu yuru ga nutsukamu story come on
Everybody stand up! Today's the best time to get up!
everybody stand up agero kyou ichiban no jikan da
Before my eyes you still don't stop, speed hunter.
me ni mo tomaranu speed hunter
Everyone is a victim to that attraction, Yeah! (Come on!)
daremo ga mina toriko kanban yeah come on
Everybody Hands up! It's the highly anticipated Hero's Come Back!
everybody hands up matashita na hero's come back
Hold up your fingers and count down.
zujou kazoe yubi oru count down
Let's go, 3-2-1 make some noise!
ikuze 3-2-1 make some noise
Are you ready for a few risks?
hey yo whoa tashou no risuku wa kakugo desho
You have to get up no matter how many times you fall. (Get it on!)
nanka korundatte tatsu get it on
It's not some conspiracy, just a paper-thin session
nare ai ja nai ze kami hitoe no sesshon
The pent up feelings turn into a crystal.
irikunda kanjou kidzukiageta kesshou
The rising cheers will become your courage.
wakiagaru kansei ga yuuki tonaru
So stand up now, no matter how much pain you feel.
tachiagareba ima ijou kurushimi tomonau
But in the end I'm sure you'll laugh.
soredemo saigo wa kitto warau
Everything will be swept away in victory and cheer.
subete sarau shouri to kansei
Everybody stand up! Today's the best time to get up!
everybody stand up agero kyou ichiban no jikan da
Before my eyes you still don't stop, speed hunter.
me ni mo tomaranu speed hunter
Everyone is a victim to that attraction, Yeah! (Come on!)
daremo ga mina toriko kanban yeah come on
Everybody Hands up! It's the highly anticipated Hero's Come Back!
everybody hands up matashita na hero's come back
～♪
Hold up your fingers and count down.
zujou kazoe yubi oru count down
Let's go, 3-2-1 make some noise!
ikuze 3-2-1 make some noise
Run, Kankuro
（デイダラ）ハハハッ
Damn you!
（砂すなの里さとの忍）おのれ
（デイダラ）あ？ おっと
（バキ）
あ… すぐに攻撃を中止しろ
Cease fire immediately!
We might hit Kazekage-sama.
風影かぜかげ様に当たるやもしれん
（砂の里の忍）あ… はい 攻撃中止
Y-Yes sir!
Cease fire!
（砂の里の忍）攻撃中止
Stop the attack!
（砂の里の忍）攻撃やめ
G-Gaara...
（カンクロウ）が… 我愛羅があら
What in the world is he after...?
（バキ）
一体ヤツの狙いは なんだ？
（カンクロウ）あ
（バキ）ん
Is he going to leave the village?!
里の外に出る気かよ
My man Sasori must really
be tired of waiting for me by now.
いいかげん サソリの旦那も
待ちくたびれてるころだ うん
（バキ）
ク… 生かしたまま連れ帰る気か
Is he going to take him
away alive?!
逃がすかよ
I won't let him get away!
（バキ）カンクロウ
Kankuro!
Don't be running off carelessly!
うかつに飛び出すな
隊を組むまで待つんだ
Wait until we can get
a unit together!
We'll lose him if
we just sit around!
グズグズしてたら見失うだろ！
（バキ）すぐに あとを追う
１人で深追いするな
I'll catch up soon!
Don't go after him too far
on your own!
（カンクロウ）ああ 分かってるぜ
Yeah...! I know!
チッ
That jerk was after Gaara
from the start?!
（カンクロウ）
はなっから我愛羅 狙いかよ 野郎が
Kankuro-dono!
（砂の里の忍）カンクロウ殿
絶対 逃がすんじゃねえぞ
Don't let him get away,
no matter what!
Yes, sir!
（砂の里の忍たち）はっ
He landed...?!
（カンクロウ）降りた？
There should be a unit
securing that area there...
あそこは１部隊が固めてるはずだが
My mission is accomplished.
（デイダラ）おいらのノルマは
クリアーだ うん
You're late...
（サソリ）遅えぞ
待たせんなっつったろ
I told you not to keep me waiting!
そいつは勘弁だ 結構
強かったんだ こいつが ハッ
Cut me some slack...
This guy was pretty strong.
（サソリ）だから もっとちゃんと
準備しとけって言ったんだ
That's why I told you to make sure
you were prepared.
How about the preparations here?
（デイダラ）こっちの準備は？
Things are all ready here.
（サソリ）バッチリだ
時間は たっぷりあったし
I had plenty of time, you see...
I was fully prepared unlike you.
お前と違って 準備も十分だ
（デイダラ）フッ
Then, let's get out of here.
じゃ 引き上げだな うん
I'll never be back here again...
もう ２度と 来ることもねえな
Hold it!
（カンクロウ）止まれ
（砂の里の忍）どうしました？
What is it...?
It's too quiet...
（カンクロウ）
やけに静かすぎるじゃん
（砂の里の忍たち）ああ…
里の出入り口は１部隊が固めていた
There was a unit securing
the village entrance.
そこに敵が降りてくれば
大きな騒ぎになっているはず
There should be quite a commotion
if the enemy landed there...
And yet, I don't hear
a single thing!
なのに 咳払い１つ聞こえねえ
それに さっきから
何度か伝令を送っているのに
And... I've been sending
several messages,
yet there hasn't been
a single response.
１度として返ってこねえ
一体どうなってるんだ？
What the hell's going on here?!
（砂の里の忍）ああ
K-Kankuro-dono!
か… カンクロウ殿
What is it?!
どうした？
ああ！
Wh-What's this...?!
な… なんだこれ？
ムチャクチャじゃんよ
What a mess...
（砂の里の忍たち）あ… ああ
They weren't attacked just now...
今やられたんじゃねえ
It might've been before Gaara
started to fight...
恐らく我愛羅が戦い始める前だ
There were even elite Anbu Black Ops
members here...
班には精鋭もいたのに
They must have been attacked at once
by a rather large group?
よほどの人数で
一気に攻めてきたのか？
Or perhaps...
あるいは…
Perhaps...?
（砂の里の忍）あるいは？
No. It's nothing...
いや なんでもねえ
I made a thorough investigation
（カンクロウ）
我愛羅が風影に就任するときに
徹底的に調べたんだ
when Gaara took
the Kazekage position...
砂隠れの忍に
裏切り者なんか いるわけねえ
No way could there be a traitor
among the Hidden Sand Shinobi!
（カンクロウ）この様子だと
我愛羅をさらった連中は
From the looks of this,
the guys who took Gaara just
passed straight through here.
ここを素通りして行ったようだな
Hurry! We're going after them!
（カンクロウ）急いで追うぞ！
（砂の里の忍たち）はっ
- Yes, sir!
はっ まだ息がある者が…
There's someone still alive!
Stop! Don't move him carelessly...
よせ うかつに動かすな！
うん あ！
A paper bomb?!
起爆札
ああ
（砂の里の忍たち）
うわっ うわあ！
（カンクロウ）く… くっ
（デイダラ）
サソリの旦那のトラップに
ひっかかったようだな
It looks like they fell for your trap,
Sasori my man.
（サソリ）フッ 当たり前だ
Of course. Traps are made
to be fallen into.
引っかかるように作るのが
トラップってもんだ
（デイダラ）なるほどね うん
I get it.
I'm home! I've come back, now!
(うずまきナルト)たっだいま
今 帰ってきたってばよ
Whoa! Just as I'd expect,
さすがに何年も ほっとくと
ホコリだらけだってばよ
things get pretty dusty when
you leave it for years!
ん…
プハッ
サスケ 俺 帰ってきたってばよ
Sasuke... I'm back...
（ナルト）お前を連れ戻すためにな
And I'm here to get you back...
（砂の里の忍たち）あ…
It... It can't be...!
（バキ）ば… バカな
（砂の里の忍）これでは 風影様を
連れ戻しに行った連中は…
This means the group
that went to get Kazekage-sama
back has been...
まさかカンクロウまで…
Don't tell me...
they got Kankuro, too...
（バキ）ああ！ 離れろ 崩れるぞ！
Get back! It's going to collapse!
（砂の里の忍たち）ああ
What's that?!
あれは…
う…
K-Kankuro...
か… カンクロウ
２人しか助けられなかった
I was only able to save
two of them...
（砂の里の忍）う… うう
（砂の里の忍）あ… ああ
（カンクロウ）
こいつらケガをしてる 治療を頼む
These guys are hurt!
Get them some medical attention!
（バキ）お前は どうするんだ？
What're you going to do?!
Isn't it obvious?!
（カンクロウ）
決まってるじゃんか！
I'm going to get Gaara back!
我愛羅を連れ戻す
Kankuro...!
カンクロウ 我愛羅を
倒したほどのヤツだ
He was strong enough
to beat Gaara!
You don't stand a chance against him!
お前だけでは どうにもならん
So are you saying we should
just forsake Gaara?!
だからって我愛羅を
放っておけってのか
（バキ）そうは言ってない
That's not what I'm saying!
アジトさえつかめれば あとで
隊を組んで攻めることもできる
If we can just find out
where their hideout is,
we can form a unit later
and attack!
I guess I can't stop him, huh...?
止めるのは無理か
Listen up! Just follow them...
いいか 追尾するだけだ
絶対に手を出すな
Don't even think about
making a move!
Yeah... If I can!
ああ できたらな
（バキ）チッ カンクロウのヤツ
That Kankuro...!
あ…
（カンクロウ）
クッ… なめやがって
They're mocking me...
あ…
あ！
Is it Gaara's sand...?!
(カンクロウ)我愛羅の砂が…
Hang on... Gaara!
待ってろよ 我愛羅
（バキ）ええい ここは任せる
I leave this to you!
- Yes, sir!
（２人）はっ
Deploy a pursuit unit and
have them go after Kankuro immediately!
追跡部隊を出し すぐに
カンクロウのあとを追わせろ
Yes, sir!
（砂の里の忍）はっ
And contact the Hidden Leaf immediately
regarding this situation!
（バキ）それと木こノ葉は学園に
この事態を至急連絡しろ
Tell them it's an emergency! Got it?!
緊急事態だと いいな
Yes, sir!
（砂の里の忍）はっ
I have a bad feeling about this...
嫌な予感がする 何か…
何かが起り始めている
Something...
Something's about to happen...!
頼んだぞ タカ丸まる
I'm counting on you, Takamaru!
行け
Go!
（男の子）風影様
Kazekage-sama...
（母親）大丈夫よ きっとすぐに
戻ってきてくださるわ
It'll be fine. I'm sure he'll come back
right away...
あ
く…
This way, huh?!
こっちか
（はたけカカシ）はあ すばらしい
Wonderful...
ついつい２回も読み返してしまった
I couldn't help reading it
over twice...
そろそろ寝るか
I guess I should get to bed...
あ… あれ？ もう朝か
Huh...? It's already morning...?
おっと いかん
Uh-oh... Not good.
新チームの招待リスト
まだ作ってなかった
I still haven't made the unit list
for the new team.
Not good, not good at all...
いかん いかん
ん？
あれ どこだっけ 書類は？
Where did I put...
those documents again?
あ… あれ？
（テマリ）よし
All right...!
（奈良ならシカマル）
どうしたんだ こんな早くに
What're you doing up so early...?
（テマリ）あっ
（シカマル）まだ
みんな寝てる時間だぜ
Everyone's still sleeping,
you know.
（テマリ）お前…
You...?!
あまり長く 里を空けておく
わけにも いかんからな
I can't leave the village unattended
for too long...
要件が済んだら できるだけ早く
帰ろうと思っただけだ
My business here is finished,
so I just thought I'd head back
as soon as possible...
朝飯も食わずにか？
Without even eating breakfast?
途中で茶屋でも見つけて食う
I'll just find a teahouse or something
along the way and eat there.
お前こそ こんなとこで
何をしている？
What're you doing here?
めんどくせーけどよ
It's a pain, but I'm supposed
to be your guide.
俺は あんたの案内係って
ことになってるからな
任務だから しょうがねえ
I have no choice seeing
as how it's a mission.
ご苦労なこった
Must be quite a hassle...
ここでいい
Here is fine...
（シカマル）次に会うのは
中忍ちゅうにん試験のときだな
The next time we meet,
we will be at
the Chunin Exams, huh?
ああ それじゃあな
Yeah... See you around...
あ？
お前も早く上忍じょうにんになれ
It's about time you become
a Jonin.
面倒くさいなどと言わず 真面目に
任務をこなせば すぐなはずだぞ
It'll happen before you know it
if you stop saying stuff's a pain
and just carry out your missions...
ああ… んん～
フッ
え… めんどくせー
What a pain...
よっしゃあ
All right!
(春野はるのサクラ)いよいよね
At last!
（テマリ）嫌な風だ
I don't like this wind...
あっ どうした？ サソリの旦那
What is it, Sasori my man?
（サソリ）まさか
ついてくるヤツがいるとはな
I never thought...
someone would be following us.
（カンクロウ）待て！
（デイダラ）ん？
Hold it!
見つけたぞ
I found you...!
我愛羅は返してもらうぜ
You will return Gaara to me!
（デイダラ）フッ
（サソリ）
デイダラ お前は先に行け
Deidara... You go on ahead...
（カンクロウ）ああ！
（カンクロウ）
確か おかしな鳥を使って
As I recall...
he was the one who took Gaara
using that strange bird...
我愛羅をさらって行ったのは
あいつだったよな
Then this must be the guy
who set the trap in the village...
じゃあ こいつは里に
トラップを仕掛けたヤツか
（サソリ）ん？
カラクリ演劇見せてやるぜ
I'll show you... my puppet show!
烏からす！
Crow!
黒蟻くろあり！
Black Ant!
山椒魚さんしょううお！
Salamander!
もう１度 言う
我愛羅は返してもらう
I'll say it again...
You will give Gaara back to me!
（ナルト）おっそい！
You're late!
（サクラ）やっと来た
Finally, you're here...
（カカシ）いやあ
悪わりい 悪わりい
Gee, sorry about that...
今回は 新チームの書類 書くのに
普通に手間取ってな
This time it took longer
than I thought
to write up the documents
for the new team.
Today's our new team's first mission!
Aren't you fired up?!
きょうから俺たち新チームの
初任務なんだぞ
気合い入ってねえってばよ
カカシ先生って
昔から そんなんだもんな
You've always been like that,
Kakashi-sensei!
ああもう いきなりうるさい！
Oh, come on.
You're already annoying!
元から気合いの抜けた顔なんだから
しょうがないでしょ カカシ先生は
It can't be helped.
Kakashi-sensei's always had
that look of disinterest!
（カカシ）
威厳なくなってきてるなあ 俺…
I'm starting to lose
my dignity here.
（鳥の鳴き声）
（カカシ）あ… ん？
あれは確か 砂隠れの…
If I'm not mistaken,
that's one of the Hidden Sand's...
（サソリ）傀儡くぐつの術か
Puppet Master Jutsu, huh...?
（デイダラ）フッ
じゃあ おいらは先に行くぜ
Then I'm going on ahead!
行かせるか！
You're not going anywhere!
（デイダラ）はっ
ああ
な…
Wha--?!
（サソリ）
俺は 人を待つのも待たすのも
好きじゃねえからな
I don't like waiting for people,
and I don't like
making people wait...
すぐに終わらせる
I'll finish this right away.
When I look up at the sky.
sora wo miagereba
♪～
The stars, see, are sparkling.
hoshitachi ga hora matataiteru
Each giving off its own light.
kono hoshi no hitotachi mitai ni
Like the people on this planet.
samazama na hikari wo hanatte
Yeah, so among them, I too,
sono naka de boku mo
want to shine particularly bright.
hitokiwa kagayaite itain da
I close my eyes and make a vow in my heart,
me wo tojite kokoro ni chikau
and entrust my dreams to that shooting star.
nagareboshi ni yume wo takushite
I'm in my usual park.
koko wa itsumo no kouen
I can see the night scenery on the slide.
yakei ga mieru suberidai no ue
That's been my special seat for years.
mukashi kara boku no tokutouseki
Whenever I'm worried about something, I come here.
nayami ga areba koko ni kurun desu
Just like then, I'm on my way to my dreams.
ano koro no mama yume no tochuu de
But unable to fulfil them.
ima de kanaerarezu ni irun desu
Maybe this is the end of the line.
moshikashite koko ga mou shuuten
There are days when I say weak things like that.
nante yowane wo haite shimaisou na hi mo aru
But every time, I remember.
demo sono tabi ni omoidasu
That starry sky where I looked for a shooting star.
nagareboshi wo sagashite ano hoshizora
The wish I made when I was little hasn't changed even now.
chiisana koro no negaigoto ima mukashi mo kawaranai mama
When I look up at the sky.
sora wo miagereba
The stars, see, are sparkling.
hoshitachi ga hora matataiteru
Each giving off its own light.
kono hoshi no hitotachi mitai ni
Like the people on this planet.
samazama na hikari wo hanatte
Yeah, so among them, I too,
sono naka de boku mo
want to shine particularly bright.
hitokiwa kagayaite itain da
I close my eyes and make a vow in my heart,
me wo tojite kokoro ni chikau
～♪
and entrust my dreams to that shooting star.
nagareboshi ni yume wo takushite
Next Episode
With his brother's life at stake,
it looks as though this is a match
さあ 挑戦者
カンクロウにとっては
弟の命運を賭けた
負けられない１戦だが
that the Challenger Kankuro
cannot afford to lose?!
Well, he is  one of the finest
Puppet Masters in the Hidden Sand.
彼は 砂隠れきっての
傀儡師ですからね
Meanwhile, the Champion Sasori
has yet to show his skills,
一方 チャンピオンサソリは いまだ
手の内を見せない不気味な存在だ
making his presence even creepier!
Wow, Kankuro made the first move
by bringing out his Crow!
おおっと カンクロウ
先手必勝 烏を繰り出した
あっさり止められましたね
And it just went down...
However, the challenger still has
an ace known as the Salamander....
でも 彼には まだ山椒魚という
隠しだねがありますからね
Wow, and just as we speak,
there's the Salamander!
おおっと 言ってるそばから
山椒魚だ
What sort of trick will it display for us?!
はたして どんなギミックを
見せてくれるのか？
Next time: "Team Kakashi, Deployed"
次回
「出撃、カカシ班」
Team Kakashi, Deployed
Leaf Village
Sightseeing
Society
The Society for Leaf Tourism
今回は中忍試験の
第２試験会場にも使われた…
Today, I'll be reporting
on the 44th Training Ground,
第四十四演習場
also known as “The Forest of Death”,
44TH TRAINING GROUND
通称 死の森を
レポートするぜ
which was used as the second exam site
for the Chunin Exams!
This training area is circular with
a radius of ten kilometers
この演習場は こんなふうに
半径10キロメートルの
円状になってて
and is surrounded by a wire fence.
周りは ぐるっと金網で囲われてる
During the exams,
俺たち受験者は
we broke up into our teams starting
out from the 44 locked gates
鍵のかかった44個のゲートから
チームごとに分かれて
and all tried to reach
the tower in the center of the area.
真ん中の塔を目指したんだ
Check out these huge trees.
見てくれよ このバカでっけえ木
And it's not just the trees that are huge.
でっかいのは木だけじゃねえぜ
The centipedes, leeches and tigers
are all huge
ムカデもヒルもトラも全部でかくて
おまけにムチャクチャ凶暴
and totally ferocious on top of that!
When I recall how they made us
battle for scrolls in a place like this...
こんなところで 巻物の争奪戦を
させられてたかと思うと
Ugh, I get chills just remembering.
ああ… 思い出しただけで
寒気がするってばよ
このデンジェラスな森を
かすり傷１つなく突破できたら
If you can get through this dangerous forest
without a scratch,
you just might be able
to approach the skills of Gaara!
君も我愛羅に近づけるかも
This has been Uzumaki Naruto reporting
以上 木ノ葉きっての野生の宝庫
from the greatest reservoir
of nature in the entire Leaf...
死の森から
うずまきナルトが
お届けしたぜ
the Forest of Death!
T
o
b
e
c
o
n
t
i
n
u
e
d
.
Tune in again!